{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20closest%20star%20to%20Earth%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sun",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Alpha%20Centauri",
        "Proxima%20Centauri",
        "Sirius"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20Red%20Planet%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mars",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Venus",
        "Jupiter",
        "Mercury"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20planet%20is%20known%20as%20the%20'ringed%20planet'%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Saturn",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Jupiter",
        "Uranus",
        "Neptune"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20planet%20in%20our%20solar%20system%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Jupiter",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Saturn",
        "Neptune",
        "Uranus"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20dwarf%20planet%20beyond%20Pluto%20that%20was%20formerly%20known%20as%20the%20ninth%20planet%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Eris",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ceres",
        "Haumea",
        "Makemake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20nearest%20galaxy%20to%20the%20Milky%20Way%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Andromeda",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Triangulum",
        "Orion",
        "Sombrero"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20farthest%20point%20from%20the%20Earth%20within%20our%20solar%20system%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Kuiper%20Belt",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Oort%20Cloud",
        "Heliopause",
        "Asteroid%20Belt"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20first%20artificial%20satellite%20launched%20into%20space%20by%20humans%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sputnik%201",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Explorer%201",
        "Vanguard%201",
        "Apollo%201"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20largest%20moon%20in%20our%20solar%20system%2C%20orbiting%20Jupiter%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Ganymede",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Titan",
        "Europa",
        "Callisto"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20astronomer%20proposed%20the%20three%20laws%20of%20planetary%20motion%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Johannes%20Kepler",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Nicolaus%20Copernicus",
        "Galileo%20Galilei",
        "Isaac%20Newton"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
